[
    {
        
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "What is the full meaning of A.I",
        "optionA": "Artificial Intelligence",
        "optionB": "Artificial Instruction",
        "optionC": "Automated Instruction",
        "optionD": "Automated Intelligence",
        "answer": "Artificial Intelligence"
    },
    {
        
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "Google was founded in what year?",
        "optionA": "1997",
        "optionB": "1998",
        "optionC": "1999",
        "optionD": "2000",
        "answer": "1998"
        
    },
    {
        
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "Documents that can only be seen but not touched are known as?",
        "optionA": "Hardware",
        "optionB": "Software",
        "optionC": "Spyware",
        "optionD": "Scareware",
        "answer": "Software"
     
    },
    {
        
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "An example of semi conductor memory device is",
        "optionA": "USB Flash Drive",
        "optionB": "Floppy Disc",
        "optionC": "Compact Disc",
        "optionD": "Tape",
        "answer": "USB Flash Drive"
    },
    {
        
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "Facebook was created in what year",
        "optionA": "2002",
        "optionB": "2003",
        "optionC": "2004",
        "optionD": "2005",
        "answer": "2004"
    },
    {
        
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "A family of computer networking technologies commonly used is in LAN, MAN and WAN is",
        "optionA": "Internet",
        "optionB": "Ethernet",
        "optionC": "Sharenet",
        "optionD": "Intranet",
        "answer": "Ethernet"
    },
    {
        
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "Java was designed by?",
        "optionA": "Richard Benson",
        "optionB": "James Gosling",
        "optionC": "Guido van Rossum",
        "optionD": "Dennis Ritchie",
        "answer": "James Gosling"
    },
    {
      
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "Programs that are meant to kill other virus are known as",
        "optionA": "Anti-virus",
        "optionB": "KIller virus",
        "optionC": "Virus",
        "optionD": "Malware",
        "answer": "Anti-virus"
    },
    {
       
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "Which of the following is not an output device?",
        "optionA": "Mouse",
        "optionB": "Monitor",
        "optionC": "Keyboard",
        "optionD": "Printer",
        "answer": "Mouse"
    },
    {
        
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "Convert 3 to base 2",
        "optionA": "100",
        "optionB": "11",
        "optionC": "10",
        "optionD": "111",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "Who is often refered to the father of computers?",
        "optionA": "Blaize Pascal",
        "optionB": "John Napier",
        "optionC": "James Gosling",
        "optionD": "Charles Babage",
        "answer": "Charles Babage"
    },
    {
        
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "Trial test of a computer or software or app before the commercial launch is called",
        "optionA": "Test Run",
        "optionB": "Beta Test",
        "optionC": "Dry Running",
        "optionD": "Product checking",
        "answer": "Beta Test"
    },
    {
       
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "A family of computer networking technologies commonly used is in LAN, MAN and WAN is",
        "optionA": "Internet",
        "optionB": "Ethernet",
        "optionC": "Sharenet",
        "optionD": "Intranet",
        "answer": "Anti-virus"
    },
    {
       
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "The second generation computers used?",
        "optionA": "Vacum tubes",
        "optionB": "Transistors",
        "optionC": "Integrated circuts",
        "optionD": "Batteries",
        "answer": "Transistors"
    },
    {
        
        "type": "Computer science",
        "question": "What does RAM mean?",
        "optionA": "Read Access Memory",
        "optionB": "Random Asset Memory",
        "optionC": "Random Access Memory",
        "optionD": "Read Accept Memory",
        "answer": "Random Access Memory"
    }
]